Ricketts mss. III, 1856-1979 LMC 1831
Lilly Library
- Financial
  - Invoices
    - St. Ignatius College, 1904 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - St. James Church, Chicago, 1911-1926 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - St. James High School, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Saint Joseph Stock Yards Co. - Missouri, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - St. Joseph's Hospital, Chicago, 1909-1912 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - St. Louis National Stock Yards - Missouri, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - St. Luke's Church - Evanston, Illinois, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - St. Mark's Parish - Evanston, Illinois, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - St. Mary's Church - Park Ridge, Illinois, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - St. Mary's School - Clinton, Iowa, 1913-1917 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - St. Paul Union Stock Yards Co. - Minnesota, 1907 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Salvation Army Board of Chicago, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Schmidt, Otto L., 1912-1928 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Scholarship Association for Jewish Children, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - School Book Publishers of Chicago, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - School of Filing, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Scott, Schofield, Knapp, Stilwell, Schoonmaker, Cunningham, 1910 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Scully Steel and Iron Co., 1914 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Security Bank of Chicago, 1911-1925 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Serta Matress Co., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Shedd, John G., 1910-1914 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      See also: Munroe and Southworth
    - Shellmar Products Co., 1938 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Shepard, Mrs. Thomas Hill, 1908 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Shore Acres - Lake Bluff, Illinois, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Sigma (in care of Helen Ricketts), 1915 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Sigma XI Fraternity, 1916-1922 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Signode Steel Strapping Co., 1940 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Silver, Burdett and Co., 1911-1912 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Skokie Country Club, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Slaught, Henry E., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Society of Grain Elevator Superintendents, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Sojourners Club, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Sons of the American Revolution - Illinois Society, 1922-1925 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - South Park Commissioners, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Southern Investment Co., 1912 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Spaulding Graded School - Barre, Vermont, 1912-1916 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Spencer, W. H., 1919 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Spoeri, W. G., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - The Standard Club - Chicago, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - The Standard Office Building Corp., 1936-1941 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Standard Railway Equipment Manufacturing Co., 1939 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Stanley Hall - Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1903-1921 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Stanley Publishing Co., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - State Historical Society of Iowa, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - State Savings Loan and Trust Co. - Quincy, Illinois, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - State Street Council - Chicago, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - State Street Merchants Association, 1908-1915 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Stavanger Cathedral Association, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Steel and Tube Company of America, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Stevan School for Girls - Chicago, 1912-1916 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - The Stevens Hotel, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Stevens, Maloney and Co., 1917 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Stewart-Warner Corp., 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Stock Yards National Bank and Stock Yards Trust and Savings Bank, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Stock Yards Savings Bank, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Stordock, Perry G., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Storrer, John, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Straus, Henry H., 1935-1937 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Streeter Hospital - Chicago, 1908-1914 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Struggles, Miss, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Swedish Baptist Theological Seminary, 1913-1921 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Swift, Harold H., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Swift and Company, 1911-1920 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Superintendents' Club, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Syracuse University - New York, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Tau Beta Pi, 1936-1942 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Taylor, Fannie, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Temple Sholom - Chicago, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Tennessee Orthopaedic Group, 1971-1977 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Thornton Township School - Harvey, Illinois, 1908-1922 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Thurber Art Galleries - Chicago, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Tracy Lodge, No. 810 A.F. and A.M., 1911 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - The Traffic Club of Chicago, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Trans-Continental Freight Co., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Tremont Lumber Co., 1922 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Truax-Traer Coal Co., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Turner, Oliver S., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - UARCO, Inc., 1957-1968 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Underwriters Laboratories, Inc., 1962 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Union League Club of Chicago, 1907-1918 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Union Park Lodge, No. 610, A.F. and A.M., 1917 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Union Stock Yard and Transit Company, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Union Trust Co. - Chicago, 1912-1915 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - United Breweries Co., 1916 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - United States Cold Storage Co., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - United States Fuel Administration, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - United States Gypsum Co., 1909-1917 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - United States Shipping Board, Emergency Fleet Corp., 1919 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - United World Federalists - Chicago, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - University Club - Chicago, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - University of Chicago, 1899-1961 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - University of Illinois - School of Pharmacy Alumni Association, 1908-1921 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Uptown National Bank - Chicago, 1942-1953 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Utilities Securities Co., 1923 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Vehon, W. H., 1914 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Viroqua, Wisconsin - Board of Education, 1908 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Wacker-Wabash Corp., 1965 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - Wade, J. C., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - Walter, Ardys, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - Walton, Lyman A., 1908 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - Wagner, Albert W., 1910-1911 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - Warman, Cy, 1894 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - Washington Boulevard Hospital, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - A Waukegan Conservatory of Music, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - The Wayfarers - Chicago, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - Welcome Lodge, No. 918, A.F. and A.M., 1912 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - Wells, Arthur F., 1907 (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Wells, F. A., 1904-1906 (Box 17, Folder 124)
    - Wells-Gardner and Co., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 125)
    - Wells Lamont Co., 1969 (Box 17, Folder 126)
    - Wendell, Barrett, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    - Werner Co., Encyclopedia Dept. (Encyclopedia Britannia), 1896 (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Wesley College - Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1938-1941 (Box 17, Folder 129)
    - West Side Trust and Savings Bank - Chicago, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 130)
    - Western Military Academy - Alton, Illinois, 1926-1971 (Box 17, Folder 131)
    - Western Paper Dealers' / Merchants Association, 1911-1918 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    - Western Traffic Executive Committee, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 133)
    - Western Trunk Line Committee, 1937-1940 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 135)
    - Whiting Corporation, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - Wieboldt, Mrs. W. A., 1926 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - William C. Baade and Co., 1912 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - Williams, Lewis W., 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Wilson, John P., 1942 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - Wilson, Lou M., 1896 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - Wilson and Co., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    - Wilson Brothers, 1918-1925 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    - Wing, L. M., 1923 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    - Winnebago National Bank - Rockford, Illinois, 1914-1921 (Box 17, Folder 145)
    - Winnetka (village), Illinois, 1935-1942 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - Winnetka Bible Church, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - Winnetka, Illinois - Board of Education, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 148)
    - Winnetka Caucus Committee, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - Winnetka Congregational Church, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - Winnetka Institute for Hearing and Speech, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - Winnetka Parent-Teacher Association, 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - Winnetka Public Library, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - Wisconsin Alumni Association, 1950-1962 (Box 17, Folder 154)
    - Woman's Athletic Club, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    - World's Columbian Exposition, 1894-1915 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    - Wolf, Walter B., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    - World's Sunday School Association, 1911-1917 (Box 17, Folder 158)
    - Wormser, Leo F., 1925 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - Wright, E. L., 1915 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - Young, George W., 1895 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - Young Men's Christian Association - Chicago, 1916-1941 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - Young Men's Christian Association - Evanston, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    - Young Men's Jewish Council, 1944-1955 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - Youngquist, Ida W., 1908-1912 (Box 17, Folder 165)
      Youngquist was a doctor whom CLR consulted
    - Ziegfeld Club - Chicago, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - Medical receipts, 1887-1905 (Box 17, Folder 167)
    Includes doctor, hospital, pharmacy bills, prescriptions, and recommended diets
  - Medical receipts, 1906-1909 (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - Medical receipts, 1910-1929 (Box 17, Folder 169)
  - Medical receipts, 1930-1939 (Box 17, Folder 170)
    Includes doctor, hospital, pharmacy bills, prescriptions, and recommended diets [lb] For 1939 there are medical bills and cancelled checks for the last illness of Hettie (Merriam) ricketts and her burial expenses
  - Medical receipts, 1940-1957 (Box 17, Folder 171)
  - Medical receipts, undated (Box 17, Folder 172)
  - North Shore Syndicate papers, 1890-1900 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    Papers of a syndicate formed to acquire a tract of 46 acres at Wilmette, Illinois. Includes legal papers, letters, receipts, and statement of purpose
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1883-1899 (Box 17, Folder 174)
    Includes property in Minnesota and Illinois. CLR at one time owned a home in Michigan, but it may not show up in these folders
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1900-1910 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1911-1914 (Box 17, Folder 176)
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1915-1919 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1920-1927 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1928-1933 (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Property deeds and real estate taxes, 1934-1948 (Box 17, Folder 180)
- The Scriptorium
  - The Alphabet
    - The Alphabet by J. M. R. (Julia Marguerite Ricketts), 14 January 1923 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Two alphabet strips; one lettering of "Alexander Hamilton Institute"; one undated alphabet strip with the names of Helen (Ricketts) Goodman's children (her daughter was born in Dec. 1922 and her son in Nov. 1918)
    - The Alphabet by Charles W. Norder, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Negative only with holograph comment by Jasper S. King
    - The Alphabet by H. A. Rounds, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Compliments by H. A. Rounds and sample of penmanship
    - Specimens of the alphabet in various ornate styles (Box 37)
    - Twenty-one examples in pen and pencil (1 dated 1891 by CLR, 1 dated 1925 by CLR) (Box 53)
  - Latin Bible - Vulgate, 1462, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Description of the Bible brought into The Scriptorium by Hans G. Kellerman, with a note in the hand of Jasper S. King
  - A Century of Progress - Book of Records (Box 40)
  - The Book
    "The Book" was prepared by C. L. Ricketts to illustrate the development of the alphabet from the 7th to the 15th centuries as found in medieval documents
    - Collected notes (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - 1. Book of Darrow. Trinity College, Dublin. Fols 77v and 118. 7th century (Box 35)
    - 2. Lindisfarne Gospels. British Museum. Cotton ms., Nero D. IV. Fols. 10v, 15v, 17, 29. ca. 700 A.D. (Box 35)
    - 3. Lindisfarne Gospels. Fols. 19, 91, 139v, 203v, 204 (Box 35)
    - 4. Lindisfarne Gospels. Fols. 5v, 18v, 90, 131, 131v, 208 (Box 35)
    - 5. Lindisfarne Gospels. Fol. 3 (Box 35)
    - 6. Lindisfarne Gsopels. Fol. 139r (Box 35)
    - 7. Lindisfarne Gospels. Fol. 90 (Box 35)
    - 8. Book of Kells. Trinity College, Dublin. Fol. 8 from Summary of the Gospels. 8-9th century (Box 35)
    - 9. Book of Kells. Fol. 114v. St. Matthew (Box 35)
    - 10. Book of Kells. Fols. 15v, 16v, 19 (Box 35)
    - 11. Book of Kells. Leaf of monogram initials with folios noted (Box 35)
    - 12. Book of Kells. Leaf of initials (Box 35)
    - 13. Book of Kells. Fols. 122v, 185v, 230v (Box 35)
    - 14. Book of Kells. Fol. 173v (Box 35)
    - 15. Psalter of St. Augustine, Canterbury. British Museum. Cotton ms., Vespasian A.I. Fol. 33. 8th century (Box 35)
    - 16. Bede's Ecclesiastical History. British Museum. Cotton ms., Tib. C.I. Fol. 5v. 8th century (Box 35)
    - 17. Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. Folio 4. Celtic, 9th century? (Box 47)
    - 18. Bede's Ecclesiastical History. Cotton ms., Tib. A. XIV. Letters A-U. 9th century (Box 35)
    - 19. Bede's Eccles. Hist. Cotton ms., Tib. A. XIV. Capital letters and HIS (Box 35)
    - 20. Psalter. Salisbury Cathedral. Ms. 150. Initials with folios noted. A. D. 969 (Box 35)
    - 21. Psalter, Hymnal. British Museum. Add. Ms. 37517. Initials. 10th century (Box 35)
    - 22. Psalter. British Museum. Arundel ms. 155. Fol. 93. A.D. 1012-23 (Box 35)
    - 23. Grimbald Gospels. British Museum. Add. Ms. 34890. Fol. 10v. 11th century (Box 35)
    - 24. Various Tables, Pictures. British Museum. Cotton ms., Tib. C. VI. Fol. 31. A.D. 1041-1066 (Box 35)
    - 25. Various Tables, Pictures. British Museum. Cotton ms. Tib. C. VI. Vols. 10, 60 (Box 35)
    - 26. Psalter. British Museum. Arundel Ms. 60. Fol. 13. ca. A.D. 1060 (Box 35)
    - 27. Psalter. Arundel Ms. 60. Fol. 85 (Box 35)
    - 28. Epistles of St. Paul. Trinity College Library, Cambridge. Ms. B. 5. Fol. 8v. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 29. St. Eadwin's Psalter. Trinity College Library, Cambridge. Ms. 17. I. Initials, A-V. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 30. Hrabani Mauri. British Museum. Royal Ms. 12 G. XIV. Initial. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 31. Psalter. British Museum. Cotton ms. Nero C. IV. Fol. 46. A.D. 1160 (Box 35)
    - 32. Works of Flavius Josephus. British Museum. Royal ms. 13. D. VII. Fols. 62, 74v, 138v, 153, 161, 187. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 33. Psalter. St. John's College, Cambridge. Ms. C. 18. Initials A-?. 12th century. Folios noted (Box 35)
    - 34. Psalter. British Museum. Harley Ms. 5102. Fol. 1. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 35. Psalter. Harley ms. 5102. Initials A-V (Box 35)
    - 36. Psalter. Harley ms. 5102. Fols. 49v and 49. Incomplete (Box 35)
    - 37. Westminister Psalter. British Museum. Royal ms. 2.a. XXII. Fols. 15 and 147. 12th century (Box 35)
    - 38. Bible. British Museum. Royal ms. I.D.I Fol. 350v. 13th century (Box 35)
    - 39. Bible. Royal ms. I.D.I. Fol. 397v (Box 35)
    - 40. Bible. Royal ms. I.D.I. Initials A-V (this is not No. 48) (Box 35)
    - 41. Bible. British Museum. Royal ms. I.B. XII. Initials A-U with folios noted. A.D. 1254 (Box 35)
    - 42. Bible. British Museum. Add. Ms. 15253. Initials A-W. A.D. 1270 (Box 35)
    - 43. Oscott Psalter. Perrins ms. 11. Initials A-U. 13th century (Box 35)
    - 44. Oscott Psalter. Fols. 232b and 233 (Box 35)
    - 45. Petrus Comestor. Historica Scholastica. British Museum. Royal ms. 3.D. VI. Fol. 234. A.D. 1283-1300 (Box 35)
    - 46. Ormesby Psalter. Bodleian Library, Oxford. Douce 366. Initials, first quire, with folios noted. A.D. 1300 (Box 35)
    - 47. Ormesby Psalter. Initials, second quire (Box 35)
    - 48. Ormesby Psalter. Fol. 109. Two copies, one a hand-colored photo. Lacks label. Information on verso of second copy (Box 35)
    - 49. Missale Fratrum Menorum. British Museum. Add. Ms. 36616. Initials A. E. C. M. D6. 14th century. Incomplete (Box 35)
    - 50. Missale Fratrum Menorum. Add. Ms. 36616. Initials N, R, P, S, Q, U (Box 35)
    - 51. Breviary. British Museum. Stowe Ms. 12. Initials A-U. A.D. 1325 (Box 35)
    - 52. Breviary. Stowe Ms. 12. Fol. 25v (Box 35)
    - 53. Breviary. Stowe Ms. 12. Fol. 62 (Box 35)
    - 54. Liber de Officiis Regum. Christ Church Library, Oxford. Ms. 72. Fols. 21v and 37v. A.D. 1327 (Box 35)
    - 55. Psalter of Queen Philippa. British Museum. Harley Ms. 2899. Fols. 34v, 86v. A.D.1328-40 (Box 35)
    - 56. Psalter. British Museum. Arundel Ms. 83. Fol. 72. A.D. 1339 (Box 35)
    - 57. Bible. British Museum. Add. Ms. 29704-5. Initials composing the word SCRIPTORIUM. A.D. 1384 (Box 35)
    - 58. Bible. British Museum. Royal Ms. I.E. IX. Initials with folios noted. 14th century (Box 35)
    - 59. Bible Royal Ms. I.E.IX. Historiated initials (Box 35)
    - 60. Hours. British Museum. Royal Ms. 2.A.XVIII. Fols. 34, 53. A.D. 1399 (Box 35)
    - 61. Missal. John Rylands Library, Manchester. Lat. Ms. 136. Fol. ?. A.D. 1405 (Box 35)
    - 62. Commentary on the Psalms. Trinity College Library, Cambridge. Ms. B.5.25. Fol. 118. 15th century (Box 35)
    - 63. Wichkelife's Bible. John Rylands Library, Manchester. Eng. Ms. 217. Fol. 40v, 124. 15th century (Box 35)
    - 64. Sherborne Missal. Library Duke of Northumberland, London. Fols. 13 and 51. 15th century (Box 35)
    - 65. Hours. Bodleian Library, Oxford. Ms. Auct. D. infra II. 11. Fol. 231v. 15th century (Box 35)
    - 66. Abingdon Missal. Bodleian Library, Oxford. Digby 227. Fol. 113v. A.D. 1464 (Box 35)
    - 67. Abingdon Missal. Digby Ms. 227. Fol. IIIV (Box 35)
  - Bookplates by Ricketts/The Scriptorium (folder 1) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Bookplates by Ricketts/The Scriptorium (folder 2) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Bookplates by Ricketts/The Scriptorium (folder 3) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bookplates by Ricketts/The Scriptorium (folder 4) (Box 53)
  - Calendars - Ricketts, C. L. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Calligraphy album (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Certificates and Diplomas
    Awards prepared for scholastic, training session, or some specified achievement
    - Design materials - lettering, places, titles, etc. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Design materials - terminology (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Design materials - visuals (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Specifications for ordering diplomas, with note about care of diploma (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Specimens, 1892-1969
      Dates refer to those found in the material. Arranged alphabetically by school or institution
      - American Board of Pediatrics, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - American Hospital Association, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Artists Guild of Chicago, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Bradley Polytechnic Institute, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Buena Vista College, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Carl Schurz High School, Chicago, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Carroll College, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - Central YMCA High School, Chicago, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Chicago College of Dental Surgery, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Chicago College of Law, 1902 (Box 18, Folder 47)
      - Chicago Latin School, 1927-1951 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - Chicago Training School, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - Colorado College, 1901 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Cook County Normal School, 1895 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Council for Biomedical Careers, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Dearborn Seminary, 1890s (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Downers Grove Community High School, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Duke University, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Evanston Hospital Association, 1956-1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Evanston Hospital School of Nursing, 1929-1951 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - The Fairies Riding School, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Glenbard High School - Glyn Ellyn, Illinois, 1933-1935 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Highland Park High School, 1939-1942 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Hobart High School, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Illinois Farm Supply Co. - Market Leader certificate, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Illinois Institute of Technology, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - International College, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - International Technological Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Iowa Wesleyan University, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Knox College, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Lake Geneva High School, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Lewis Institute, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Loretto and University Hospitals, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Loring School, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Maine Township High School, 20th century (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Marquette University, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Mary Thompson Hospital, 1904 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Mid-American Hearing Foundation, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Nashota House/Seminary - Wisconsin, 1957-1965 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - The National School of Electricity, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - New York Life Insurance Co., undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Northwestern Military Academy, 1908 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Notre Dame High School - Chicago, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - The Policlinic Hospital Training School for Nurses, 1890s (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - St. Charles Community High School, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Saint Gregory Choir School, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Saint Scholastica - Chicago, 20th century (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Savanna Township High School, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Thornton Fractional Township High School, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Union Theological Seminary, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Whiting High School, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - York Community High School, 20th century (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - The Faulkner School for Girls, 1933-1969 (Box 46)
      - Frances Shimer School/Junior College, 20th century (Box 46)
      - Francis W. Parker School, 1920-1930 (Box 46)
      - Garrett Biblical Institute/Theological Seminary, 1890-1962 (Box 46)
      - The Gunn School of Music and Dramatic Art, 1926 (Box 46)
      - The Harvard School for Boys, 1928-1930 (Box 46)
      - Hastings College, 1926-1930 (Box 46)
      - Harverstraw Public School, New York, 1890s (Box 46)
      - Huntington College, 20th century (Box 46)
      - Huron College, South Dakota, 1927 (Box 46)
      - Illinois College, 1930-1948 (Box 46)
      - Illinois Training School for Nurses, undated (Box 46)
      - Institute of Meat Packing, 1927-1928 (Box 46)
      - Investment Bankers Association of America, 1949 (Box 46)
      - Lake Forest High School, 1939-1947 (Box 46)
      - Lake Forest Public Schools, 1933-1953 (Box 46)
      - Lake Forest University, 1953 (Box 46)
      - Lakeside Hospital Training School for Nurses, 20th century (Box 46)
      - Libertyville Township High School, 1943-1954 (Box 46)
      - Loyola University, Chicago, 1930 (Box 46)
      - Lyons Township High School, 1931 (Box 46)
      - McCormick Theological Seminary, 1920-1964 (Box 46)
      - Meadville Theological School, 1930 (Box 46)
      - Milwaukee-Downer Seminary, 1920-1930 (Box 46)
      - Muskegeon High and Hackley Manual Training School, 1920 (Box 46)
      - Muskegeon Public Schools, 1931 (Box 46)
      - Academy of Our Lady/College of Our Lady - Chicago, 20th century (Box 47)
      - Acme Steel Company, undated (Box 47)